Guide to the Samuel Stark Film and stage stars: photographs, 1911-1969
Department of Special Collections
- Peters, House (Box 12, Folder 930)
- Petina, Irra (4), (1 o.s.) (Box 12, Folder 931)
- Phillips, Dorothy (Box 12, Folder 932)
- Pickford, Jack (Box 12, Folder 933)
- Pickford, Mary (9) (autographed) (3 o.s., 1 signed) (Box 12, Folder 934)
- Pidgeon, Walter (4) (autographed) (1946) (Box 12, Folder 935)
- Pierce, James (3) (1928) (Box 12, Folder 936)
- Piro, "Killer" Joe (3) (press release and newspaper clipping) (dancer) (Box 12, Folder 937)
- Pistel & Cushing (autographed) (Box 12, Folder 938)
- Pitts, Zasu (1935) (Box 12, Folder 939)
- Pons, Lily (7) (1936, 1937) (Box 12, Folder 940)
- Porter, Paul (1922), (autographed) (Box 12, Folder 941)
- Post, Guy Bates (Box 12, Folder 942)
- Powell, Dick (12) (1936, 1937) (Box 12, Folder 943)
- Powell, Eleanor (see also Allen, Gracie) (43) (1937), (4 o.s.) (Box 12, Folder 944)
- Powell, William (18) (1937, 1938) (autographed), (1 o.s.) (Box 12, Folder 945)
- Power, Tyrone (3) (Box 12, Folder 946)
- Powers, Tom (2) (Box 12, Folder 947)
- Preisser, June (4) (Box 12, Folder 948)
- Presley, Elvis (Box 12, Folder 949)
- Preston, Ann (1936?) (Box 12, Folder 950)
- Prevost, Marie (Box 12, Folder 951)
- Pryor, Roger (1934) (Box 12, Folder 952)
- Purcell, Irene, (1 o.s.) (Box 12, Folder 953)
- Quigley, Jane (4) (1935) (Box 12, Folder 954)
- Quinn, Anthony (2) (Box 12, Folder 955)
- Quinn, Carmel (2) (1963) (Box 12, Folder 956)
  (write-up) (singer)
- Raft,George (8) (1934) (Box 12, Folder 957)
- Rainer, Louise (6) (1936, 1937), (2 o.s.) (Box 12, Folder 958)
- Rains, Claude (3), (1937) (Box 12, Folder 959)
- Raitt, John (2) (Box 12, Folder 960)
- Ralston, Esther (3), (1936) (Box 12, Folder 961)
- Rambeau, Marjorie (Box 12, Folder 962)
- Rand, Sally (2) (1928, 1939) (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 963)
- Rathbone, Basil (3) (Box 13, Folder 964)
- Rawlinson, Herbert (1936) (Box 13, Folder 965)
- Ray, Charles (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 966)
- Raye, Martha (11) (1936, 1937, 1938) (Box 13, Folder 967)
- Raymond, Gene (11) (1936, 1937) (Box 13, Folder 968)
- Reagan, Ronald (2) (1937), (1 o.s.) (Box 13, Folder 969)
- Reed, Barbara (4) (1937) (Box 13, Folder 970)
- Reed, Florence (Box 13, Folder 971)
- Reed, Phillip (3) (1935), (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 972)
- Reid, Wallace (3), (autographed reproduced) (Box 13, Folder 973)
- Reilly, Betty (Box 13, Folder 974)
- Revere, Anne (2) (Box 13, Folder 975)
- Reynard, E. (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 976)
- Rhodes, Minnie (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 977)
- Riabouchinska, Tatiana, (1 o.s.) (Box 13, Folder 978)
- Rice, Florence (9) (Box 13, Folder 979)
- Rich, Irene (3) (autographed) (3 o.s.) (Box 13, Folder 980)
- Richmond, Harry (Box 13, Folder 981)
- Rin Tin Tin (autographed - Yes! Rin Tin Tin can write!) (Box 13, Folder 982)
- Ritchard, Cyril (Box 13, Folder 983)
- Ritz Brothers (Box 13, Folder 984)
- Robert, Muriel, (1 o.s.) (Box 13, Folder 985)
- Roberts, Edith (Box 13, Folder 986)
- Roberts, June (Box 13, Folder 987)
- Roberts, Thayer (Box 13, Folder 988)
- Roberts, Theodore (4) (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 989)
- Robinson, Bill (5) (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 990)
- Robinson, Edward G (9) (1936, 1937) (Box 13, Folder 991)
- Robson, May (15) (1912, 1936, 1937), (1 o.s.,signed) (Box 13, Folder 992)
- Rogers, Charles, (1 o.s.) (Box 13, Folder 993)
- Rogers, Ginger (13) (1936, 1937) (Box 13, Folder 994)
- Rogers, Will (24) (1933, 1935) (autographed reproduced) (Box 13, Folder 995)
- Roland, Gilbert (4) (1931) (Box 13, Folder 996)
- Roland, Ruth (2) (Box 13, Folder 997)
- Rollins, David (2) (Box 13, Folder 998)
- Romero, Cesar (see Vera-Ellen file) (6) (1935, 1936, 1937) (Box 13, Folder 999)
- Rooney, Mickey (24) (1933) (Box 13, Folder 1000)
- Rorke, Hayden (Box 13, Folder 1001)
- Rose, Billy (Box 13, Folder 1002)
- Rosita, Eva (3) (Box 13, Folder 1003)
- Ross, Lany (2) (1934) (Box 13, Folder 1004)
- Ross, Shirley (9), (1936, 1938) (Box 13, Folder 1005)
- Roth, Lillian (5),, (1929, 1931) (Box 13, Folder 1006)
- Rounseville, Robert (2) (Box 13, Folder 1007)
- Rub, Christian, (1 o.s.) (Box 13, Folder 1008)
- Rubens, Alma (Box 13, Folder 1009)
- Ruggles, Charles (8), (1936) (Box 13, Folder 1010)
- Ruiz, Machna (Box 13, Folder 1011)
- Russell, Anna (14) (commedienne) (Box 13, Folder 1012)
- Russell, Jane, (1 o.s.) (Box 13, Folder 1013)
- Russell, Lillian (empty folder) (Box 13, Folder 1014)
- Russell, Rosalind (25) (1936, 1937) (4 o.s.) (Box 13, Folder 1015)
- Russell, Zella (Box 13, Folder 1016)
- Ruth, Babe (1931) (baseball player), (1 o.s.) (Box 13, Folder 1017)
- Rutherford, Ann (6) (1936) (Box 13, Folder 1018)
- StDennis, Ruth (2), (1916) (autographed) (dancer) (Box 13, Folder 1019)
- StJohn, Al (3) (Box 13, Folder 1020)
- Saki, Marion (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 1021)
- Sale, Chic (4) (1916, 1931, 1932) (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 1022)
- Salisbury, Monroe (Box 13, Folder 1023)
- Samuels, Ray (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 1024)
- Sandlin, Dorothy (2) (Box 13, Folder 1025)
- Sanford, Randee (2) (Box 13, Folder 1026)
- Sarnoff, Dorothy (2) (Box 13, Folder 1027)
- Salvo, Jimmy (1931) (Box 13, Folder 1028)
- Sayers, Dora (Box 13, Folder 1029)
- Schildkraut, Jos (2) (1929) (Box 13, Folder 1030)
- Schildkraut, Rudolph (Box 13, Folder 1031)
- Schmitz, E.E. (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 1032)
- Schoop, Trudi (3) (autographed) (comic ballet) (Box 13, Folder 1033)
- Scofield, Paul (1962) (autographed) (Box 13, Folder 1034)
- Scott, Fred (Box 13, Folder 1035)
- Scott, Mary (Box 13, Folder 1036)
- Scott, Randolph (10) (1933, 1934, 1935) (Box 14, Folder 1037)
- Searle, Judith (Box 14, Folder 1038)
- Sebastian, Dorothy (Box 14, Folder 1039)
- Segal, Vivienne (autographed) (Box 14, Folder 1040)
- Seldes, Marian (4) (Box 14, Folder 1041)
- Sellers, Peter (Box 14, Folder 1042)
- Selwyn, Ruth (2) (1931, 1932) (Box 14, Folder 1043)
- Shafer, Robert (Box 14, Folder 1044)
- Shannon, Leona, (1 o.s.) (Box 14, Folder 1045)
- Shannon, Peggy (5) (1931) (Box 14, Folder 1046)
- Sharif, Omar (Box 14, Folder 1047)
- Shaw, Lola (Box 14, Folder 1048)
- Shaw & Lee (Box 14, Folder 1049)
- Shawn, Ted (4) (dancer) (1943, 1944) (autographed) (Box 14, Folder 1050)
- Shearer, Norma (27) (1923, 1931, 1932, 1934, 1935) (4 o.s.) (Box 14, Folder 1051)
- Sheridan, Ann (15) (4 o.s.) (Box 14, Folder 1052)
- Sherman, Lowell (4) (autographed) (Box 14, Folder 1053)
- Sherwood, Gale (Box 14, Folder 1054)
- Shirley, Ann (2) (1936, 1939, 1941) (Box 14, Folder 1055)
- Sidney, George (2) (1934) (Box 14, Folder 1056)
- Sidney, Sylvia (10) (1933, 1934, 1936, 1937, 1938) (Box 14, Folder 1057)
- Sills, Milton (6) (1928) (autographed) (Box 14, Folder 1058)
- Simon, Simone (1936) (Box 14, Folder 1059)
- Simpson, Ivan (1935) (Box 14, Folder 1060)
- Sims, Mae (2) (autographed) (Box 14, Folder 1061)
- Singleton, Penny (Box 14, Folder 1062)
- Skelly, Hal (2) (1929) (Box 14, Folder 1063)
- Skelton, Red (Box 14, Folder 1064)
- Skibine, George (see Antonia Cobos file) (Box 14, Folder 1065)
- Skinner, Cornelia Otis (12) (Box 14, Folder 1066)
- Skinner, Maud (autographed) (Box 14, Folder 1067)
- Skinner, Otis (2) (Box 14, Folder 1068)
- Skipworth, Alison (3) (1933) (Box 14, Folder 1069)
- Slavenska (5) (dancer) (Box 14, Folder 1070)
- Sleeper, Marta (5) (1934, 1935) (3 o.s.) (Box 14, Folder 1071)
- Smith, C. Aubrey (2) (1935) (Box 14, Folder 1072)
- Smith & Dale (Box 14, Folder 1073)
- Smith, Kate (6) (1932, 1933, 1943) (Box 14, Folder 1074)
- Smith, Queenie (1936), (1 o.s., signed) (Box 14, Folder 1075)
- Smith, Stanley (autographed) (Box 14, Folder 1076)
- Snow, Marguerite (Box 14, Folder 1077)
- Snyder, Louise (autographed, reproduced) (Box 14, Folder 1078)
- Sokoloff, Vladimir (2) (Box 14, Folder 1079)
- Solar, Willie (autographed) (Box 14, Folder 1080)
- Sondergaard, Gale (1936) (Box 14, Folder 1081)
- Sothern, Ann (20) (1934, 1935, 1936, 1937), (1 o.s.) (Box 14, Folder 1082)
- Sothern, E.H. (9) (Box 14, Folder 1083)
- Sparks, Ned (1935) (Box 14, Folder 1084)
- Stafford, Grace (3) (Box 14, Folder 1085)
- Stander (2) (1936) (Box 14, Folder 1086)
- Standing, Ser Gay (1936) (Box 14, Folder 1087)
- Stanley, Forrest (2) (autographed, reproduced) (Box 14, Folder 1088)
- Stanwyck, Barbara (24) (1931, 1932, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1941) (autographed, reproduced), (2 o.s.) (Box 14, Folder 1089)
- Stapleton, Maureen (Box 14, Folder 1090)
- Starke, Pauline (3) (Box 14, Folder 1091)
- Starr, Frances (2) (Box 14, Folder 1092)
- Stephens, Harvey (Box 14, Folder 1093)
- Sterling, Ford (Box 14, Folder 1094)
- Sterling, Jan (2) (Box 14, Folder 1095)
- Stevens, Onslow (2) (Box 14, Folder 1096)
- Stewart, Anita (2) (1937) (Box 14, Folder 1097)
- Stewart, James (9) (1936) (Box 14, Folder 1098)
- Stone, Carol (2) (Box 14, Folder 1099)
- Stone, Dorothy (2) (dancer) (Box 14, Folder 1100)
- Stone, Fred (8) (1936,1937) (Box 14, Folder 1101)
- Stone, George (1935) (Box 14, Folder 1102)
- Stone, Lewis (8) (1931) (autographed) (Box 14, Folder 1103)
- Stuart, Gloria (3) (1932, 1933) (Box 14, Folder 1104)
- Stuart, Nick (3) (Box 14, Folder 1105)
- Stuart, Robert (Box 14, Folder 1106)
- Sullavan, Margaret (24) (1935, 1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 14, Folder 1107)
- Summerville, Slim (12) (1930, 1932, 1933) (Box 15, Folder 1108)
- Sunderland, Nan (1927) (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1109)
- Suratt, Valeska (1 o.s., signed) (Box 15, Folder 1110)
- Swanson, Gloria (16) (1934, 1936, 1937) (6 o.s., 3 signed, 1 to Sam Stark) (Box 15, Folder 1111)
- Swarthout, Gladys (14) (1935, 1936) (Box 15, Folder 1112)
- Sweet, Marjorie (Box 15, Folder 1113)
- Swickard, Joseph (1936) (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1114)
- Swor, Bert (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1115)
- Talbor, Lyle (Box 15, Folder 1116)
- Taliafero, Edith (3) (1927) (Box 15, Folder 1117)
- Talmadge, Constance (1 o.s., signed) (Box 15, Folder 1118)
- Talmadge, Norma (3) (Box 15, Folder 1119)
- Tamiroff, Akim (Box 15, Folder 1120)
- Tanguay, Eva (2 o.s., 1921) (Box 15, Folder 1121)
- Tannen, Julius (2) (1934) (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1122)
- Tashman, Lilyan, (1 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1123)
- Taylor, Estelle (Box 15, Folder 1124)
- Taylor, Kent (Box 15, Folder 1125)
- Taylor, Laurette (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1126)
- Taylor, Megan (Box 15, Folder 1127)
- Taylor, Robert (7) (1937) (4 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1128)
- Tearle, Conway (2) (Box 15, Folder 1129)
- Tedrow, Irene (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1130)
- Temple, Shirley (12) (child star) (1933, 1934, 1935, 1936) (Box 15, Folder 1131)
  (copy from baby book of important events)
- Terry, Ellen (see Sam Stark Scrapbook Collection for more) (Box 15, Folder 1132)
- Terry, Phillip (Box 15, Folder 1133)
- Theilade, Nini (ballet dancer) (Box 15, Folder 1134)
- Thomas, John Charles (4) (singer)(2 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1135)
- Thompson, Fred with his horse Silver (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1136)
- Tibbett, Lawrence (2) (Box 15, Folder 1137)
- Tip, Tap, and Toe (3 tap dancers) (Box 15, Folder 1138)
- Tobias, George (comedian) (Box 15, Folder 1139)
- Tobin, Genevieve (8) (autographed) (1934) (Box 15, Folder 1140)
- Tobin, Vivian (2) (Box 15, Folder 1141)
- Tomack, Ben and Isabelle plus letter (5) (dancers) (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1142)
- Tone, Franchot (7) (Box 15, Folder 1143)
- Torrence, Ernest (Box 15, Folder 1144)
- Torres, L (Box 15, Folder 1145)
- Toumanova, Tamara (ballet dancer) (Box 15, Folder 1146)
- Tracy, Lee (Box 15, Folder 1147)
- Tracy, Spencer (7), (1 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1148)
- Treacher, Arthur (2) (Box 15, Folder 1149)
- Treadwell, Lois (2) (dancer) (Box 15, Folder 1150)
- Tree, Dorothy (2) (Box 15, Folder 1151)
- Tremayne, Chris (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1152)
- Trevor, Claire (Box 15, Folder 1153)
- Truex, Ernest (Box 15, Folder 1154)
- Tucker, Sophie (2) (1944) (autographed), (2 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1155)
- Tucker, Richard (1925) (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1156)
- Turner, Lana (5), (1 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1157)
- Turpin, Ben (comedian) (autographed, reproduced) (Box 15, Folder 1158)
- Tyers, John (2) (Box 15, Folder 1159)
- Tynon, Richard (1937) (Box 15, Folder 1160)
- Ulric, Lenore (2) (1925) (6 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1161)
- Vain, O.B. (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1162)
- Valdes, Miguelito (dancer) (Box 15, Folder 1163)
- Valentino, Rudolph (7) (Box 15, Folder 1164)
- Vallee, Rudy (4) (1946) (autographed), (1 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1165)
- Vara, Sarita (Box 15, Folder 1166)
- Vedder, William (Box 15, Folder 1167)
- Velez, Lupe (8) (1943) (Box 15, Folder 1168)
- Veloz and Yolanda (10) (dancers) (1 o.s., signed to John Stein) (see Stark Scrapbook Collection for more) (Box 15, Folder 1169)
- Venable, Evelyn (1934) (Box 15, Folder 1170)
- Vera-Ellen (2) (Box 15, Folder 1171)
- Verdera, Clare (Box 15, Folder 1172)
- Verdon, Gwen (2) (dancer) (Box 15, Folder 1173)
- Verebes, Erno (Box 15, Folder 1174)
- Vernille, Nitza, (1 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1175)
- Victor, Charles (Box 15, Folder 1176)
- Vickers, Joan (no photos, see Louis Treadwell file) (Box 15, Folder 1177)
- Vicor, Florence (Box 15, Folder 1178)
- Vilan, Demetrios (autographed) (dancer and director) (Box 15, Folder 1179)
- Villar, Charles (autographed) (1928) (Box 15, Folder 1180)
- Wagner, Jack (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1181)
- Walker, Marie Louise (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1182)
- Wallace, Beryl, (1 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1183)
- Wallach, Eli (Box 15, Folder 1184)
- Walsh, G. (Box 15, Folder 1185)
- Walthall, Henry (Box 15, Folder 1186)
- Warfield, David (autographed) (1920) (Box 15, Folder 1187)
- Warrenton, Lulu (Box 15, Folder 1188)
- Warwick, Robert (Box 15, Folder 1189)
- Washburn, Bryant (2) (Box 15, Folder 1190)
- Walburn, Raymond (1936) (Box 15, Folder 1191)
- Waters, Ethel (2) (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1192)
- Watkins, Linda (8) (Box 15, Folder 1193)
- Watson, Harry, Jr (Box 15, Folder 1194)
- Wayne, John (2) (1937, 1942) (Box 15, Folder 1195)
- Weaver, Marjorie (Box 15, Folder 1196)
- Webb, Clifton (Box 15, Folder 1197)
- Weber and Fields (Box 15, Folder 1198)
- Webster, George (autographed) (1915) (Box 15, Folder 1199)
- Weidler, Virginia (autographed) (1936) (Box 15, Folder 1200)
- Weissmuller, Johnny (5) (Box 15, Folder 1201)
- Welch, Niles (Box 15, Folder 1202)
- Welford, Nancy (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1203)
- Welles, Orson (2) (1938) (Box 15, Folder 1204)
- West, Mae (21) (autographed) (1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1946, 1970) (Box 15, Folder 1205)
- West, Willie (3) (Box 15, Folder 1206)
- Weston, Ruth (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1207)
- Whelan, Arleen (4) (Box 15, Folder 1208)
- White, Alice(2 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1209)
- White, Francia (Box 15, Folder 1210)
- White, Pearl (2) (Box 15, Folder 1211)
- White, Sammy (Box 15, Folder 1212)
- Whiteman, Paul (Box 15, Folder 1213)
- Whiting, Jack (Box 15, Folder 1214)
- Wilcox, Henry (Box 15, Folder 1215)
- Wilde, Patricia (ballet dancer) (Box 15, Folder 1216)
- Williams, Earle (Box 15, Folder 1217)
- Williams, Emlyn (3) (Box 15, Folder 1218)
- Williams, Hope (Box 15, Folder 1219)
- Wills, Iva(2 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1220)
- Wilson, Lois (2) (Box 15, Folder 1221)
- Wilson, Marie (4) (1941) (Box 15, Folder 1222)
- Windsor, Claire (2) (Box 15, Folder 1223)
- Winston, Nadine (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1224)
- Winwood, Estelle (2)(2 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1225)
- Wise, Tom (Box 15, Folder 1226)
- Withers, Jane (5) (1935, 1936, 1937) (Box 15, Folder 1227)
- Wolff, Franchon (7) (1937) (Box 15, Folder 1228)
- Wong, Anna M(4), (1934) (Box 15, Folder 1229)
- Wood, Edward (Box 15, Folder 1230)
- Wood, Peggy (3) (Box 15, Folder 1231)
- Woodward, Henry (Box 15, Folder 1232)
- Woollcott, Alexander (Box 15, Folder 1233)
- Woollwy, Monty (1946) (Box 15, Folder 1234)
- Wray, Fay (2) (Box 15, Folder 1235)
- Wright, Theresa (2) (1941) (Box 15, Folder 1236)
- Wyman, Jane (4) (also see Ronald Reagan), (1 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1237)
- Wynn, Ed, (1 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1238)
- Yaconelli, Ed, (1 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1239)
- Yarr, Sonya (Box 15, Folder 1240)
- Young, Clara (5) (1916) (autographed) (Box 15, Folder 1241)
- Young, Loretta (14) (1937) (Box 15, Folder 1242)
- Young, Robert (13) (Box 15, Folder 1243)
- Yousevitch, Igor (4) (ballet dancer) (Box 15, Folder 1244)
- Yule, Joe (Box 15, Folder 1245)
- Zanuck, Darryl, (1 o.s.) (Box 15, Folder 1246)
- undetermined (11) (ballet dancers) (Box 15, Folder 1247)
- Oversized photographs (Box 17)
- Oversized photographs (Box 18)
- Oversized photographs (Box 19)